Sorry to keep you waiting. I know until now
I will report the situation
This is the paper you have
Anyway, for now, read aloud
Let me do it. In this
Of our ship headquartered in Germany
Bernhard Schulte Shipmanagement (BSM) managing
That
The company is currently using the ship (Kokuka Courageous)
Khor Fakkan, which is a UAE port,
Like pulling a ship (Kokuka Courageous) on it with a tag board
Work has begun.
I said yesterday about this matter
As I said, by this accident
The Vessel (Kokuka Courageous)
Damage has occurred.
Therefore, take care of the crew
Has all been departed once.
Then the U.S. military
Crew members are all supported
I boarded the ship again, until now
Of the ship that was not functioning
The backup power supply has been restored. Currently, Kokuka Courageous
The ship is in its condition
Things are stable.
Damage such as comprehensive damage
And the like, but the sinking
There is no possibility. And
There is no loss of cargo and fuel.
One person from Kokuka Courageous
Reported minor injuries
, But this is the bullet
It ’s because of injury
When jumping into the sea when leaving the ship,
I jump into the sea, so at that time
Is still unknown
is. However, U.S. military ships
At the time of boarding the U.S. military
I took it firmly,
Medical allowance
Because I have you
The person is on board now.
The ship (Kokuka Courageous) is now
In other words, Fujairah Port الفجيرة
By the way, 70 miles to here
Is located 16 miles offshore of Iran.
In this regard we
All have branches in Singapore
German company BSM
Abbreviation for the company Bernhard Schulte Shipmanagement I mentioned earlier.
Through the BSM.
Actively monitor and if further details are found
Separately
I will explain. that's all.
If you have any questions, please accept them. Yes.
(Question) The United States has indicated the possibility of a mine attack.
(Answer) Not at all. Because the waterline,
The sea, the point of contact between the sea surface and the ship
Because it goes above it (the damage mark)
It is definitely underwater if it is a torpedo
I don `t go. I think that is a false alarm.
(Question) This is NHK. You have released footage of the U.S. military recall, but have you seen that?
(Answer) We have not entered yet.
(Question) Have you seen the video? (Answer) Yes. On the contrary, I want to see it now
Though it is about. Regarding the news,
We have not yet entered from BSM.
Unfortunately. Not yet (that information).
(Question) Why did you say this was impossible?
(Answer) What is impossible?
(Question) Could you tell us why you said there was no mine attack?
(Answer) The basis is that the torpedo is below the surface
Because it does not collide on the water surface,
The point where the shell landed is well above the surface of the water.
So definitely
I explain that it is not a torpedo.
(Question) Number of attacks
Do you know where the damage is?
(Answer) I think I explained yesterday,
Well, it's behind the ship
Close to the fuel tank there
At first we have landed. The second shot
Yesterday, Manifold, deck
Unload the cargo above
It is where the pipe to be put is in,
Said it landed there
Information was included and entered,
So far it was a misinformation
It is feeling. For the second shot,
Near the center of
There is a small hole above the sea level
Because it seems to be like that,
This is the situation I know now.
(Question) There is a small hole on the side of the ship ...
(Answer) It's a public photo of the ship and everyone
You can see it.
It looks like it was not a deck.
(Question) What will be done in the future after the spare power of the Vessel (Kokuka Courageous) is restored? About that point. Will your company review your shipping routes in the future?
(Answer) Now, the seafarer re-boarded on board, as I said yesterday,
Inject CO2 into the engine room
Going to prevent fire
We have a regular generator etc.
To get it working again
Emissions including CO2 are discharged outboard
Otherwise you will not be able to enter the ship
Doing that first
The first problem.
And the spare power supply is in another place
So its spare power, this is the battery
There are also types
Navigating instrument after moving it
Well, I started by moving such things first.
(Question) What about then?
(Answer) After that, in the future
The ship carries 225,000 tons of methanol,
The problem of restoration, of course,
So here we are
Call Fakkan, as you write,
Although this is not fixed,
Tow this (Call Fakkan) direction
If there is a harbor, port again
Authority, only with the permission of the Port Authority
Bring it up there and there
Enter the task of transshipping luggage
We are preparing like this.
(Question) When is it going to be?
(Answer) I can not predict at all. Still tugboat
But one of them is small
It is a situation where (the ship) cannot run.
In the meantime, a US ship is nearby
Escort me, helicopter, etc.
Fly over the ship, no more
He / she assists you not to be attacked.
(Question) As your company, the impact on the operation of
(Answer) There is a possibility that it will come out, but at the moment, the route selection will be reviewed
From the Persian Gulf, when it comes to carrying luggage,
Including crude oil, unless this route is closed
The ship will be operated with the consent of the seafarers.
(Question) Do you transfer goods to your ship?
(Answer) It is not necessarily our ship.
Anyway, I want to find the earliest ship and transship to that ship.
(Question) Do you outsource operations to another company?
(Answer) Which operation?
(Question) Ship operation.
(Answer) No, we do not entrust our ship to another company.
(Question) So, you mean chartering?
(Answer) Yes. Charter and transship to another ship
Because it is
(Question) About the situation where the crew was attacked
(Answer) Regarding the matter, both from BSM and sailors.
There is no direct contact.
When I arrive at a safe port for the time being
Again from BSM Singapore
Send overseers and others,
We issue a report including the situation collection.
(Question) Is Khor Fakkan the UAE?
(Answer) Khor Fakkan is described as Oman (in the distributed material), but there is the Gulf of Oman and it is UAE.
(Question) Indicate where the second shell (receiving place) was received in the photo because it was different from the announcement yesterday
(Answer) The first shot is around here, apart from starboard and port. The second shot is around here.
You mentioned a torpedo earlier, but the torpedo has this ship and the sea surface,
Only below this line
Because the torpedo does not go, we have received (attack)
It's just above this. Since both shots are above
The torpedo has no chance.
(Question) Is it the same for mines as for torpedoes? (I'm talking about torpedoes) Is it the same for mines?
(Answer) Mines are just floating in the water. Floating or
Place the ship at a depth just below the sea surface, and explode when touched
No damage at sea level.
(Question) Is there anything (explosives) to be pasted on the side?
(Answer) What does that mean?
(Question) Like a timed bomb
(answer)
The crew of the Vessel said, "I was attacked by a flying object."
Bomb on that side
Or a time bomb,
I do not think that.
(Question) Does it mean that the crew is talking about flying objects?
(Answer) Yes.
(Question) Does the crew see the attack?
(Answer) Yes. I am watching. I do not understand the first shot.
(Question) Are you watching?
(Answer) Yes. The second shot.
(Question) What about the first shot?
(Answer) I don't know. "Something seems to have flown."
So an explosion pierced the hull
Such a report has come.
(Question) That is the first shot. Did you definitely confirm that the second shot flew visually?
(Answer) Yes. Not everyone saw it. Because people on the bridge see it.
(Question) So, do you mean that you were attacked by something that flew?
(Answer) Yes, it is.
(Question) Do you know the size of the flying object?
(Answer) I don't know at all.
(Question) How fast was the speed?
(Answer) They can't judge themselves,
I do not know.
(Question) What is the size of the hole caused by flying objects? How much
(Answer) I haven't looked into it yet.
(Question) Are the first and second shots one each?
(Answer) One by one.
(Question) Is the first shot on the starboard rear?
(Answer) Yes.
(Question) Port number 2
(Answer) Near the center. Yes yes
(Answer) (Revised) Right now, starboard and port ...
Is it true? Again, we're sorry,
We will check again, so as soon as we understand it,
Please let everyone know.
(Question) Is the first shot (where the attack was made) on the starboard side on the rear, and the second shot on the port side?
(Answer) I don't know if they are the same.
Let me check again there.
Check the location. It is certain that we received the second shot.
(Question) Is the first shot on the port side?
(Answer) From the picture
It was starboard. (But I'm not sure)
That's once again, the ship, etc.
Contact was actually made
Once again, the phone, the satellite they have
If you can connect to the phone etc.
I will check it.
(Question) What direction did you fly?
(Answer) I don't know. I don't know this at all.
Of course, because I ’m running,
I'm guessed, though.
(Question) I'd like to confirm, is it safe to say that you were on the starboard side of the first attack trace, and do you need to confirm?
(Answer) No, check both (the position of the two attacks).
Yes. I ’ll confirm, but I ’m
As far as I can remember, (the first attack) was behind the port
(Question) What did you see and remember?
(Answer) Look at the photo.
(Question) Is it a public photo?
(Answer) Yes. Yes.
(Question) Is that about the first attack?
(Answer) Yes, it is.
(Question) The second shot is on the port as far as the picture shows
(Answer) Feeling like (same port as the first shot).
(Question) Is the paper (handout) you received on the first day wrong?
(Answer) It may be wrong.
(Question) About the direction I flew ...
(Answer) Until then, we have not checked. I'm sorry.
(Question) How many US Navy escorts are there?
(Answer) There is no report on the number of vessels.
(Answer) There is no report on whether it is one or two ships.
(Question) What is the helicopter escort?
(Answer) We have received the escort of a helicopter flying off the US warship.
(Question) Did you see an Iranian ship around?
(Answer) There was an Iranian warship.
(Question) Does that mean that Iranian warships were around when the crew were rescued?
(Answer) Yes. At that point, Iran was around.
(Question) How is it currently being towed (by tugboat)?
(Answer) To that point, (information) has not yet entered.
(Question) Are American warships quite close (of the ship being towed)?
(Answer) Of course, they are running right next to the ship
(Question) Do you mean running in parallel?
(Answer) Because it is not running at the same time,
(Answer) 1 knots and 2 knots are only as fast as you walk now
(Question) Does it feel like it is attached to the tag board? (Answer) Yes
(Answer) And now, through BSM and insurance companies
Requesting
Schmidt, a salvage company in the Netherlands
This company prepares a ship with a large horsepower and reaches the ship
That means that we are working
Within 24 to 36 hours from now on, we have talked about reaching the ship and restarting towing again.
(Question) The handout document states that he is being towed,
(Answer) We are towing a small boat.
(Question) so it's slow
(Question) Is it OK that the Vessel has restored the backup power supply?
(Answer) Yes. It has been restored.
(Question) The crew is boarding the ship because I can live on the ship.
(Answer) You can live in your residential area.
(Answer) However, the engine room cannot be entered yet.
(Question) Is it OK that the engine room is not moving?
(Answer) Yes.
(Question) Vessel cannot sail on its own yet
(Answer) I didn't go that far.
(Question) When will you start injecting CO2 into the engine room?
(Answer) This is already done. There is a risk of fire when they escape, so first inject CO2 to prevent fire and fire spread
Injected for fire suppression.
(Question) What confirmed the Iranian Revolutionary Defense Force ship ...
(Confirmed) Not!
(Answer) Where did that story come from?
(Question) You mentioned earlier
(Answer) Is it a warship? I'm not saying Iranian Revolutionary Army!
(Question) Did you see the Iranian warship?
(Answer) Yes.
(Question) When did you see the Iranian warship?
(Answer) Since yesterday night of Japan time.
(Question) Isn't he seeing (Iranian warships) when rescuing the crew?
(Answer) At that time (Iranian warships) are not coming.
(Question) Did you give any instructions from the Iranian warships?
(Answer) No. Because we have not received it at all.
(Question) How far is the Iranian warship?
(Answer) Also, because they should be talking to the US military, they will not send any news to you.
(Question) Will you add a tugboat and tow in the future?
(Answer) I'm asking Schmidt (salvage company) to bring one or two ships nearby as soon as possible.
(Question) One of the crew members was injured. When was the point of the injury?
(Answer) I don't know.
(Question) In which country is the methanol in the cargo?
(Answer) Singapore and Thailand.
(Question) Please explain the location of the first attack, the second attack, and the location of the engine room with photos.
(Answer) The engine room is located below this residential area, but slightly behind. This is the first shot.
(Question) You are pointing to the port side, but ...
(Answer) Because the ship in this photo only shows port.
(Answer) Probably it was port. Please do not pursue it because it has not been confirmed.
(Question) Is that all right?
(Answer) Yes.
(Answer) The second shot is around here. Near the center of the ship.
(Question) Is the second shot the opposite?
(Answer) Yes. We will announce to you once more details are clear.
(Question) Is the hole not like a bullet, but a hole like a bullet?
(Answer) I do not know this.
(Answer) If it's a burst or a penetrating bullet,
I feel like a penetrating bullet.
(Answer) If it is a explosive bullet, it explodes in various places
It must have been harmed. It is only an estimate. Guess.
(Question) It is unclear whether starboard or port has been changed, but the first damage at the rear is also
Is there a hole in one place?
(Answer) I don't know yet. Not multiple holes,
Because it is one hole, it is not known what shape it is.
(Question) From the US military, about the cause ...
(Answer) What is the cause?
(Question) Images and photos with holes in the hull have already been published by the US military,
It is alleged that a wearable explosive was recovered in the video
(Answer) I do not see the video. We are collecting information now.
(Question) Last month (May 12, 2019) There is a similar thing that happened in the UAE,
The United States cares though.
(Question) Is there such a thing?
(Answer) What is attached?
(Question) Do you check if there is something like a torpedo mounted on the hull?
(Answer) No. In general, we sail beyond our ships.
Probably none of the ships are running while checking for wearable explosives.
(Question) There is almost no such possibility ...
(Answer) I do not.
(Question) Explosives etc. at the time of loading
Can't you imagine wearing it? ?
(Answer) Since we are loading (loading) in Saudi Arabia,
I don't think so.
(Answer) As I said earlier, if you are damaged by flying objects
Since the report is included, I think that it is not a wearing thing.
(Question) You are a flying object. Did you see more than one person?
(Answer) We do not confirm the number of people. I've heard that there are people who have seen it.
(Question)?
(Answer) There is no report.
(Question) Did you see an Iranian warship mean that the crew did?
(Answer) Of course it is.
(Question) Could you explain what is important about the strait for the shipping industry?
(Answer) The importance of the strait? Of the route? If you don't go through it, you will not be able to transport the gasoline and heavy oil we use, such as UEA. Japan is also a lifeline.
(Question) What about navigation other than the ship that had this incident?
(Answer) Are we our ships? Or do you include other ships? As long as no serious incidents occur at this point,
With the consent of the sailors, the same applies to Saudi Arabia
We plan to operate the ship.
(Question) Does it mean that you can't leave?
(Answer) Yes.
(Question) Looking at the shape of the hole you made, were you guessing it was a penetrating bullet?
(Answer) It's in the middle ...
At the rear, no damage is visible.
It's just black (in the photo).
(Question) Is the penetrating bullet a round hole?
(Answer) Yes. Looks round.
(Question) How many ships are you operating in the surrounding waters now?
(Answer) Three ships. There are three ships including this one.
(Question) Are you trying to get seafarers' consent to sail?
(Answer) With the ship's consent,
Since it is a proposition that we ensure the safety of the sailors' lives,
If they say they ca n’t go
You may have to give up your ship.
(Question) What is the most recent time that is planned?
(Answer) Currently, it is at the end of this month.
(Question) Are the other two vessels waiting somewhere?
(Answer) One ship is in the dock.
(Question) Is the tonnage of the hull the largest among your tankers?
(Answer) No, not the largest, but the third.
(Question) Will you take additional defense measures in order to navigate this area in the future?
(Answer) I don't know. I don't know what it is yet.
(Question) Is that under consideration? Do you mean that you are considering strengthening security?
(Answer) Since this is not something we can do alone, including cooperation with other companies
And then discuss all related matters, such as governments, insurance companies, etc.
If the insurance person says that there is no insurance if you go through the Strait of Hormuz,
In the unlikely event the company will be crushed
It will not be able to operate.
(Question) Did you see an untrustworthy ship approaching on the ship's radar?
(Answer) We haven't been able to investigate it yet.
(Question) Is there any information such as an untrusted ship approaching?
(Answer) Absolutely.
(Question) In the updated record of the ship, the message that you will attack now,
Or is there a crime statement after the fact?
(Answer) No.
(Question) Isn't it a warship when the crew looks at an Iranian ship?
(Answer) Maybe Iranian Navy. Confirmation has not been taken.
Previously, it was not the same event, the bombing event, but there were such cases at other times, so I guess it is probably the case.
(Question) Is there no communication when you see it?
(Answer) We can't communicate with the ship, and we can't.
(Question) (Iranian army) talking to the US military?
(Answer) Talking to the U.S. Army means that our BSM
Although the content is of course kept secret, (Iranian and US military talks)
The story of doing it seems to be coming here.
(Question) Does it mean to put a rising sun flag or a Japanese flag on a ship?
(Answer) No. Since this ship is a Panama flag, it carries the Panama flag.
(Question) Is it unlikely that you intentionally attacked because it is a Japanese ship?
(Answer) Unless we do a good survey, we do not know that the operator is Japan, so we do not think that we attacked because it is Japan.
(Question) Via a Dutch ship?
(Question) 4 explosives in May 2019 (2 tankers registered in Saudi Arabia, 1 oil tanker registered in Norway, and 1 bunker ship (fuel tanker) registered in United Arab Emirates) There is an incident,
You mentioned that the MLIT had made a cautionary recommendation, but what was the next step?
(Answer) Not taken. We don't think it would be almost impossible to put explosives in such places as the ship approached while sailing.
We will be happy to announce when new information comes in, thank you.